reshot.com 2019-12-15

# Reshot

Privacy Policy

###### 1\. INTRODUCTION

1.1. Purpose of Policy

Welcome to www.reshot.com (the "Site"). Reshot ("Company," "we" or "us") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of patrons, customers, visitors, and other users of the Site. We created this Privacy Policy (this "Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of your privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other web sites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy. Capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the same meaning given them in the reshot.com Terms of Use ("Terms of Use").

Put simply, this page explains privacy issues for our site and app.

1.2. Notice Concerning Children

We are a general audience site intended for adults, and do not direct any of our content or services at minors under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly take any action we may deem appropriate, including without limitation conducting further inquiry/investigation and/or deleting that user's account.

Put simply, this site is designed for adults not kids.

###### 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

2.1. What Basic Information Do We Collect?

In operating the Site, we may include registrations, surveys, questionnaires and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses and other contact information, credit card or other payment information for purchases, as well as profile information, ratings, reviews, audio, images and videos you submit, if any.

Put simply, we only collect normal online stuff.

2.2. What Additional Information Do We Collect?

(a) Automatic Collection. Our servers automatically recognize visitors' IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet), Internet service provider, browser type, computer platform, referring web site, date and time of access, links clicked through, and possibly other information as well. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous "traffic data" that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) Cookies. From time to time, we may use the standard "cookies" feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Site. If you create an account on our Site, we may store your email address and a unique account tracking identification code in a cookie on your computer so that the Site remembers you. Cookies also help us learn which areas of our Site are useful and which areas need improvement. Our advertisers may also use cookies on our Site. We have no access to or control over these cookies once Site advertisers have been given permission to set cookies. This Policy only covers use of cookies by the Company itself, and does not cover use of cookies by any Site advertiser. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. We may also adopt newer technologies serving some of the same functions as cookies (including by way of example only, and not of limitation, HTML 5 local storage) from time to time.

(c) Global Positioning System (GPS) Functionality. When you access our Site using a GPS-enabled (or equivalent "location-aware") device, we may collect this information from your device, and use it to provide certain location-based services, and you hereby consent to our collection and use of all such information. By way of example only, and not of limitation, we may use this information to display your distance from or your current location to other Members with whom you are "friends" or with whom you share a group (or equivalent). You may disable this functionality by altering your device settings so that location information is no longer made available, but if you do so this could negatively affect your experience while using or otherwise accessing the Site.

Put simply, again, we only collect normal online or app stuff that you are probably accustomed to sharing on other services.

###### 3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

3.1. What Does reshot.com Do With Collected Information?

(a) Personal Information. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary or appropriate to provide you with our services or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Site, to send you additional information about the Company and/or the Site, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you from time to time.

(b) Anonymous Information. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and Site activity information may also be shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(c) Use of Cookies. We may use cookies (and other technologies having similar functions, such as HTML 5 local storage) to deliver content specific to your interests, to remember you when you return to the Site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our Site may also contain cookies (or technologies with similar function). We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our Site.

(d) Disclosure of Personal Information. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Company or its affiliates, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company or of Site users, or (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of Site users or the public at large.

(e) Sale of Assets. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Site. If the Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(f) Access to Information / Opting-Out. Users may opt-out of receiving certain types of communications in the user account settings.

Put simply, we keep your information safe and only use it in ways that make the service better. We never use your information in ways we wouldn't want our own information used.

###### 4\. SECURITY

The Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we can make no assurances regarding our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse or alteration.

###### 5\. SITE AREAS BEYOND OUR CONTROL

5.1. Public Forums

The Site may include interactive forums for the exchange of information, ideas and opinions. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose personal information.

5.2. Third Party Web sites

The Site may contain links to other web sites. If you choose to visit other web sites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other web sites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those web sites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

###### 6\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

6.1. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to the Site, please submit your question at the contact us page of the Site.

6.2. Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
